fltrade.com 2017-06-06

# Binary Options & Forex Broker | FLTrade | FirstLine Pty Ltd

#####   
Privacy Policy

## Commitment

FLTrade respects the privacy of any user that accesses its site(s); therefore, the Firm is committed in safeguarding any existing or prospective clients, applicants and visitors. 

## Application

In order to open an account with FLTrade, you must first complete and send an application form attaching the required documents. By completing the application form you are requested to disclose private information in order to enable the Firm to evaluate your application and comply with relevant rules and regulations. 

This information is also used by the Firm to inform you regarding its services.

FLTrade shall not disclose to a third party, any of its clients’ confidential information unless required to do so by a regulatory authority of a competent jurisdiction; such disclosure shall occur on a ‘need-to-know’ basis, unless otherwise instructed by a regulatory authority. Under such circumstances, the Firm shall expressly inform the third party regarding the confidential nature of the information.

Clients accept and consent that FLTrade may, from time to time, contractually engage companies for statistical purposes in order to improve the Firm’s marketing; as a result, some or all of the clients’ personal data may be disclosed on an anonymous and aggregated basis only. 

## Agents

We use a card processing company for your deposits and withdrawals to and from your FLTrade trading account; This company does not retain, share, store or use any personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

## Privacy

Tracking systems used on the Firm’s site(s) may collect data detailing the pages you have accessed, how you discovered this site, the frequency of visits etc; this information is obtained in order to improve the content of the Firm’s site(s) and may also be used by FLTrade to contact you, through an appropriate mean, and provide you with any information the Firm believes to be useful.

## Choice/Opt-out 

If you no longer wish to receive any communication from the Firm, you may opt-out of by following the relevant instructions included in each communication sent by FLTrade.

You shall be notified accordingly if your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/ service provider, so you can make an informed decision as to whether or not you want to share your information with that party.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. FLTrade uses cookies on its site(s). The Firm does not link the information stored in cookies to any personally identifiable information you may submit. 

FLTrade uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie does not expire when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's ‘Help’ file.

FLTrade sets a persistent cookie for statistical purposes. Persistent cookies also enable the Firm to track and target the location and the interests of users that access the FLTrade site(s) and to enhance the experience of services offered.

Some of the FLTrade business partners use cookies on the Firm’s site(s); FLTrade has no access or control over these cookies.

## Security and Protection of your personal information

The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of the site(s) or of the services is classified as ‘Registered Information. ‘Registered Information’ is protected in many ways. You can access your ‘Registered Information’ through a password selected by you. This password is encrypted and known only to you. Your password must not be revealed to anyone. ‘Registered Information’ is safely stored on secure servers that only authorised personnel have access to via password. The Firm encrypts all personal information as it is transferred to FLTrade and thus makes all necessary effort to prevent unauthorised parties from viewing any such information.

Personal information provided to FLTrade that is not ‘Registered Information’ also resides on secure servers and is again accessible only by authorised personnel via password this information cannot be accessible by you, therefore no password shall be provided in order for you to modify this.

## Legal Disclaimer 

FLTrade reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by rules and regulations and when the Firm believes that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served. FLTrade will not be liable for misuse or loss of personal information resulting from cookies on the Firm’s site(s) that FLTrade does not have access to or control over. FLTrade will not be liable for unlawful or unauthorised use of your personal information due to misuse or misplacement of your passwords, negligent or malicious.

## Changes in this Privacy Statement 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
